

PROFILE

I'm Lukas, a self-taught software developer currently studying M.Sc. Engineering Physics at Lund University. Driven by curiosity, I constantly seek new things to learn like philosophy, math, politics, or programming. I've more than one year of experience as a full-time developer, but many more as a hobbyist.

If a picture can say more than a thousand words, a website can say more than a thousand resumés. With that I want to say that you should check out my website for a more complete picture of me. Visit: https://lukaspetersson.se/

CONTACT

PHONE:

+46 707898860

EMAIL:

<u>Lukas.Petersson.1999@gmail.com</u> GITHUB:

https://github.com/lukaspetersson

ANDROID APPS

- BookLog
- Falling Kitten
- Brännbollräknare

OTHER

- Computer for Schools project with Engineers Without Borders
- Lund Startup Fellowship fellow
- FARAD (job fair) IT-manager
- Martial art studies in China
- Liberal youth party active member
- Football player for 15 years
- Science competition semi-finalist
- Erasmus+ symposium 2017 in Genoa
- Driver's license
- Loves running

LUKAS PETERSSON

Student and Software developer

EDUCATION

M.Sc. Engineering Physics, Lund University

2019 - 2024

GPA: 4.0/4 (Swedish equivalent: 5.0/5)

Natural Science, Kungsholmens gymnasium

2015 - 2018

GPA: 3.92/4 (Swedish equivalent: 22.1/22.5)

RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

IT-Consultant, Lunicore

Nov 2019 – Present, Part time

Full Stack development for different clients. Made me comfortable working with backend development and APIs with bad documentation.

Software developer, Digital Edge

Nov 2018 – Jul 2019, Full time (weekends during Ericsson internship) Programming a robot to work as a receptionist using Vue.js for the frontend and Python for communication with the robot's limbs.

Software developer intern, Ericsson

Jan 2019 - May 2019, Full time

I made web applications using React.js and Android apps using Kotlin. Working at a huge company taught me how organizations of different sizes operates.

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCES

Substitute teacher Engelska skolan Oct – Nov 2018
Sales Assistant Hemköp Oct – Nov 2018
Entertainer TUI Summer 2018
Waiter Bedinge GK Summer 2017
Golf coach Drottningholms GK 2015 - 2017

Dishwasher Abbekås hamnkrog Summer 2015 & 2016

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

